that's why few people to get in here as
a person what we'll do
looks pretty cool
alright guys hold up hellfish we're
announcing simple little yup yup yup yup
yup you guys already guessed it if you
want your routes to be as precise as
this route look at some other ones here
oh that's pretty precise if you want
your precise your routes this precise
you need a gray panda so what we're
offering today is the Panda upgrade now
this is only for people who've bought an
eon from us oh and and a grape and I
should release and a white banner we
won't ever worry loyal t-turn your white
panda into a grey panda for only $100
how it works no we're not doing enough
to look at today we're only looking at
what will he do when we're all doing
this today bro panda upgrade 7 days
special get in right now I'm gonna post
the link right now on slack and on
Twitter uh so let's just go here to
comma I'll post this link let's post it
on Twitter upgrade your white panda
today seven seven day special so we're
doing this for one week guys for one
week if you send in your white panda we
will what if you buy the eon that's
great we'll send you a neon that's yeah
that's fine yeah okay you know what what
will let me let me make those change no
no it's not $99 no no no no no make it
$99.99 for pandas or 99.99 and gray
pandas are one ninety-nine ninety-nine
so we have to make it the sum right we
have to be fair to everybody here bear
we love fair let me make those little
changes to the product yeah or if you
buy any on with the order that's fine
too if you bought an oops if you bought
an Ian from us or you buy any on with
you
order to order we want to reward your
loyalty turn your white panda and into a
gray panda for only $100 panda upgrade
now if you just have the white pan and I
don't know you can't do that you have to
have bought a neon from us otherwise
we're gonna reject it I was in the
shower yeah I just took a shower guys
all right so
but we're offering the Panda upgrade
seven days special upgrade your white
panda today I got to make the pun about
gray it was worth it
upgrade your white panda today seven
days special and you just post this on
slack here you know post this in the
Panda channel so you don't spam
everywhere now that didn't expand the
picture so that's not as good as I hoped
alright cool funding for most of you by
now if you order we want to reward your
loyalty and then your routes can look as
good as these ones here see this once
this juice is any good they're gonna be
good
oh it's pretty good guys oh it's pretty
good when will you get to see this plot
and you are out if you buy a great Panda
you should see this in like probably
about two sprints for weeks what eons
are in stock of the 64 gig and the
midnight black one 128 you know what I'm
actually gonna remove the non midnight
black 128 because we're never getting
those back in stock that's never
happening so we're just gonna cancel
that product variant let me cancel that
right now yon variant of 128 delete bye
bye
deleted variant we got 64 gigs and we
got midnight black 128 gigs that's what
we got there's no more 128 normal those
are out of stock yeah perfect
they're never coming back in stock so
that's why they're there they're out of
stock midnight blacks are really nice no
you can't upgrade you 64 Giga yon to a
midnight Blacky on let's not get crazy
and guys we only are doing this special
for four set for seven days because it's
a huge hassle
we'd like to support people who've been
loyal to come ai you're definitely going
to want the upgrade if you want any of
the new features you're gonna get faster
calibration you're gonna get driving on
maps only with grey panda no the
midnight black rider is pretty standard
but see this quality is only possible
with a gray panda so make sure to buy
your gray Panther today where do you
send them it's written right in the
thing you just send them to our P o box
in San Francisco California we're
trading in the fusion today and that's
what we have the pan to upgrade you get
a brand new gray panda it includes all
this stuff it includes and antenna
includes an antenna mount and it of
course includes the Panda so just just
send those in turn your white panda into
a gray panda for only $100 seven days
get your ship today we can you know what
I'm going to take a look let's take a
look at what you'll be getting
take a look yeah GPS antenna has a
Python library
it's called u-blox D it's part of all
compiled it we're gonna be releasing
something better soon but just to show
you guys what you'll be getting you'll
be getting a gray and the gray right
here brand new this is the shell stream
for a new product the white panda the
grape and upgrade so you're just send in
your old looking white panda like this
one right here
what oh you're right you're right I'm
terrible we are turning the white panda
into a gray panda get your upgrade today
the upgrade the upgrade yes absolutely
right the name is what makes it so yeah
if you've bought an eon all you have to
have botany on we're gonna cancel your
order but if you buy any on with the
order we will absolutely let it go
through yes we love to bring new people
into the EON community so get your great
pandas right now
little image of a big fat arrow that
goes both ways
all right cool bye-bye scope ease bye
bye bye bye enjoy enjoy the upgrade get
your upgrade today how many upgrades if
we ordered let's say you want to check
let's just check quickly let's just see
how many we've gotten so far let's see
if this is a popular product or not
let's see let's see let's see let's see
one two three four four upgrades okay
keep them coming
daily scope is new developing this
weekend I think so I think we're gonna
do it cures never getting upgraded again
no you can't send way back after you get
grey you gotta send the white first why
would I trust you you'll upgrade to
every scope it sounds good later scope
is buy shopping icon without a you
know the URL the upgrade is going down
seven days that's it seven seven seven
alright